### Arvind Kumar Digvijai

+91-9380679646 Sari.nift@gmail.com Behance Portfolio Bangalore, India

#### **About Me**

I am a NIFT - Bangalore graduate with a total of 7 years of experience in textile/ garment and Ed-tech and e-commerce industries with knowledge in the Print sector and digital platforms. I also have experience in assisting designers for fashion shows, trade exhibits and store inaugurals.

### **Graphic Designer**

Experience

Byjus, Bangalore Graphic Designer Mar 2020 - Jun 2022

- Graphic designer and illustrator
- Emailer Design, poster, banner, ppt design, typography
- Social media posts

Untung, Bangalore Print Designer Mar 2018 - Feb 2020

- Worked on woman's wear print design
- Handled garment construction process
- Redesigned website and coordinated with Marketing to design brand materials (Tag/ wash care and size labels)
- Prepared design specification sheet for vendors after market research on trends
- Sourced fabric from different vendors

Huemn Brand - Page 3 Design Studio, Delhi Fashion Designer Oct 2016 - Feb 2018

- Designed art work for embroidery (Motif, T-shirts, Prints)
- Developed blueprint for artwork for hand embroidery
- Sourced fabric for dyeing process
- Prepared design sample for Collections

Transline Global - Export house, Bangalore Graphic Designer

Jun 2014 - Sep 2016

- Designed Graphic T shirts
- Prepared artwork according to theme base for Knit wear
- Packaging Design
- Sampling for vendors

# Arvind Mills Ltd, Gujarat Graduation Project 2014

- Worked as an Graduation Project on NedGraphics Texcelle
- Designed checks and stripes for shirting division ,CAD Solutions

## Western Clothing, Bangalore Internship 2012

- Designed shirts for mens wear
- Designed brand material (Spec Sheet, Tag, Label -Wash care, size)

#### Education

National Institute of Textile Designing Fashion Technology

2010 - 2014

**Bachelor in Textile Design** 

### **TOOLS & LANGUAGES**

- Figma
- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- After Effects
- Adobe XD
- InDesign
- Coral Draw